A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-RG 1.15 (A83-A89) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 85), 1970-1985; 1.11; 74.4 Cubic Feet; 62 standard record storage boxes - Box R2242-R2302 and R2304.
  - United States, 200
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - University of Arizona - Halophytes, 1978-1984 (Box R2269)
      - University of California - Genetic Conference, Davis, 1982-1983 (Box R2269)
      - University of California - Pest Resistance, Davis, 1977-1984 (Box R2270)
      - University of Colorado - Phytoalexins, 1977-1984 (Box R2270)
      - University of Florida - Livestock Production Conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2270)
      - University of Minnesota - Maize, 1980-1984 (Box R2270)
      - University of Wisconsin - Lectins, 1976-1983 (Box R2270)
      - Washington State University - Hemoparasitic diseases, 1979-1984 (Box R2270)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Aley, Stephen B., 1981-1983 (Box R2270)
      - Gonzales-Peralta, Carlos, 1978-1984 (Box R2270)
      - Greve, Jeffrey M., 1980-1982 (Box R2270)
      - Hajduk, S.L., 1980-1983 (Box R2271)
      - Lam, David A., 1981-1983 (Box R2271)
      - Mensch, Barbara S., 1981-1984 (Box R2271)
      - Nothnagel, Eugene A., 1979-1983 (Box R2271)
    - United States - Population Sciences, P
      - American Society for Pharmacology & Experimental Therapeutics - Contraceptive drugs Conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2271)
      - Boston College - Bioethics of assisted rhythm, 1979-1984 (Box R2271)
      - Brandeis University - Pluralism study, 1981-1982 (Box R2271)
      - Cornell University - Guatemala data, 1983-1984 (Box R2271)
      - Cornell University - Monoclonal antibodies, 1982-1984 (Box R2271)
      - East Carolina University - Ovarian regulation, 1980-1983 (Box R2271)
      - East-West Center - Population trends in Southeast Asia conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2272)
      - Guttmacher Institute - Fertility control methods, 1981-1982 1984 (Box R2272)
      - Hertz, Roy, 1980-1982 1984 (Box R2272)
      - Lapham, Robert J., 1982 1984 (Box R2272)
      - Medical College of Wisconsin - Trophoblast neoplasms conf., 1981-1983 (Box R2272)
      - Mississippi Action for Community Education - Adolescent pregnancy, 1983-1984 (Box R2272)
      - Princeton University - Chinese fertility survey, 1983-1984 (Box R2272)
      - University of California - Glycoproteins, 1980-1983 (Box R2272)
      - University of Maryland - Inhibin-F secretion, 1979-1985 (Box R2272)
      - University of Michigan - World fertility survey analysis, 1983-1984 (Box R2272)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Oocyte growth, 1982-1984 (Box R2272)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, R
      - American Academy of Arts & Sciences - Daedalus cultural literacy issue, 1980-1983 (Box R2272)
      - American Place Theatre - "Do Lord Remember Me", 1983-1984 (Box R2272)
      - Arts and Business Council - Conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2272)
      - Association of American Colleges - Women's college coalition, 1982-1984 (Box R2272)
      - Association of American Universities - Research universities conference, 1980-1983 (Box R2272)
      - Black Filmmaker Foundation, 1979-1983 (Box R2273)
      - Brooklyn College - Computer music, 1980-1984 (Box R2273)
      - Bryn Mawr College - Human studies conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2273)
      - Cabin Creek Center - Plant closings film, 1982-1985 (Box R2273)
      - California State University - Working women, 1974-1983 1985 (Box R2273)
      - Carter Family Memorial Music Center - Book, 1981-1983 (Box R2273)
      - Case Western Reserve University - History of aging conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2273)
      - Center for Southern Folklore - Beale Street history, 1982-1984 (Box R2273)
      - City University of New York - Graduate School - Ortega y Gasset conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2274)
      - Claremont University Center - African literature conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2274)
      - Columbia University - Human rights research, 1979-1984 (Box R2274)
      - Columbia University - Jay papers, 1978-1983 (Box R2274)
      - Columbia University - Polish oral history (rescinded), 1982-1983 (Box R2274)
      - Columbia University - Religious freedom conference, 1975-1985 (Box R2274)
      - Council for Basic Education - Television and education conference, 1981-1985 (Box R2274)
      - Dashow, J., 1981-1983 (Box R2274)
      - Diamond, David L., 1982-1984 (Box R2274)
      - Downtown Community Television Center, 1979-1980 1982-1984 (Box R2274)
      - East Carolina University - American music festival, 1980-1984 (Box R2274)
      - Emory University - Rethinking human rights conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2274)
      - Emshwiller, Ed, 1981-1983 (Box R2274)
      - Film Company - The Battle of Ole Miss, 1981-1982 1984 (Box R2274)
      - Fund for Arts and Science Films - "Vision of America", 1982-1984 (Box R2274)
      - Graduate Theological Union - New American religious movements, 1976-1984 (Box R2275)
      - Ho, Cordell, 1981-1982 1984 (Box R2275)
      - Howard University - Africa literature conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2275)
      - Independent Film Distribution and Marketing, 1980-1983 (Box R2275)
      - Institute for Research in History - Radicalism conference, 1979-1983 (Box R2275)
      - International Council for Educational Development - National council for foreign language, 1979-1983 1985 (Box R2276)
      - Jazzmobile, Inc., 1980-1983 (Box R2276)
      - Kozol, Jonathan, 1981-1984 (Box R2277)
      - Magic Theatre Inc. - American plays, 1983-1984 (Box R2277)
      - Marshall, Ingram D., 1981-1984 (Box R2277)
      - Museum of Holography, 1976-1984 (Box R2277)
      - National Alliance of Media Arts Centers, 1979-1984 (Box R2277)
      - National Humanities Faculty - Teaching of humanities, 1980-1983 (Box R2278)
      - New World Festival, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box R2278)
      - New York Council for the Humanities - Central America and the Caribbean conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2278)
      - New York University - Human rights conference, 1978-1983 (Box R2278)
      - New York University - Writers-at-work, 1978-1984 (Box R2278)
      - Northwestern University - American music festival, 1981-1983 (Box R2278)
      - Nunez, Victor, 1982-1984 (Box R2278)
      - Original Ballets Foundation, 1973-1984 (Box R2279)
      - Princeton University - Carter concert, 1981-1982 (Box R2279)
      - Queens College - Scope conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2279)
      - Reich Music Foundation, Inc., 1975-1976 1978-1984 (Box R2279)
      - Scripps College - Modernism conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2279)
      - Solaris Dance Theatre, 1982-1984 (Box R2279)
      - Subotnick, Morton, 1977-1984 (Box R2280)
      - Sundance Institute for Film and Television - Independent filmmakers, 1980-1984 (Box R2280)
      - Theatre, Inc. - New Phoenix Theatre - New works, 1978-1983 (Box R2280)
      - University of California - Social commitment, 1978-1984 (Box R2280)
      - University of Chicago - Creation and interpretation conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2280)
      - University of Chicago - Religion and western culture conf., 1982-1984 (Box R2280)
      - University of Minnesota - European studies/American research libraries conf., 1982-19[?] (Box R2280)
      - University of Tennessee - Medical ethics conference, 1979-1982 (Box R2280)
      - Wenner - Gren Foundation - Theatre and ritual symposium, 1980 1982-1984 (Box R2280)
      - Yale University - Ellington oral history, 1978-1984 (Box R2281)
      - Yale University - Teachers Institute, 1981-1984 (Box R2281)
    - United States - Social Sciences, S
      - Brandeis University - Youth practitioner's network, 1980-1984 (Box R2281)
      - Corporation for Public/Private Ventures - Youth unemployment, 1978-1982 (Box R2282)
      - Corporation for Public/Private ventures - Youth unemployment (suppl. material) (Box R2283)
      - National Bureau of Economic Research - Minority youth employment, 1978-1983 1985 (Box R2283)
      - Policy Studies Organization - Environmental policy, 1978-1982 1984 (Box R2284)
      - Rand Corporation - Civil Justice Institute, 1980-1985 (Box R2284)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Population studies, 1971-1980 (Box R2285)
  - Media Arts Centers, 259
    - (Media Arts Centers) (Minutes), 1981 (Box R2296)
    - Bay Area Video Coalition, 1980-1985 (Box R2296)
  - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs, 267
    - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs - California, 205
      - Chavez, John Maurice, 1978-1981 (Box R2296)
    - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs - Illinois, 216
      - Evanston - Jackson, 1976-1977 1980 (Box R2296)
    - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs - Minnesota, 226
      - Brady, Nelvia M., 1978-1982 (Box R2296)
    - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs - South Dakota, 247
      - Miyasato, Stephen J., 1978-1981 (Box R2296)
  - U.S. Education - Administration & Finance Fellowships, 268
    - U.S. Education - Administration & Finance Fellowships - Fellowships, E
      - Johnson, Sharon D., 1977-1981 (Box R2296)
  - Equal Opportunity Project in Southern United States, 275
    - (Equal Opportunity Project in the Southern Region of the U.S.), 1974-1979 1981-1982 (Box R2296)
    - NAACP - Citizenship education, 1978-1979 1981 (Box R2296)
    - National Association for the Southern Poor - Fund raising, 1981-1982 (Box R2296)
    - Southern University - Rural development, 1976-1982 (Box R2296)
    - Tuskegee Institute - Goat production, 1976-1979 (Box R2297)
    - Tuskegee Institute - Small farmers, 1976-1982 (Box R2297)
    - Urban League of Greater Little Rock, Inc., 1977-1981 1983 (Box R2297)
    - Voter Education Project, Inc., 1977-1979 1981 (Box R2297)
  - Equal Opportunity Projects, 277
    - (Economic Opportunity Projects), 1979 1981-1982 (Box R2297)
    - Brandeis University - Youth employment impact, 1983-1984 (Box R2297)
    - Columbia University - Minority access and occupations, 1982-1983 (Box R2297)
    - King Center for Non-violent Social Change - Urban education, 1983-1984 (Box R2297)
    - Manpower Demonstration Research Corp. - Youth initiative, 1983-1985 (Box R2298)
  - Brazil, 305
    - University of Bahia - Donation of equipment, 1976-1983 (Box R2298)
    - Brazil - Social Sciences, S
      - Brazilian Society for Instruction - Women's labor seminar, 1977-1981 1983 (Box R2298)
    - Brazil - University Development, UD
      - University of Bahia - Economics, 1976-1983 (Box R2299)
      - University of Bahia - Oral history and Women's studies, 1983 (Box R2299)
      - University of Bahia - Social sciences, 1980-1983 (Box R2299)
      - University of Bahia - Social sciences - Rural development, 1980-1984 (Box R2299)
  - Taiwan, 605
    - Asian Vegetable Development Center - Peet, 1976-1983 (Box R2300)
  - Thailand, 617
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, S
      - University of Thammasat - Ananya, 1981-1983 (Box R2300)
      - University of Thammasat - Economics scholarships - Local, 1971-1983 (Box R2300)
  - Indonesia, 652
    - Indonesia - University Development, UD
      - Gadjah Mada University - Anthropology, 1981-1984 (Box R2300)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Dove, 1980-1984 (Box R2300)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Economics, 1975-1984 (Box R2300)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Environmental research, 1983-1984 (Box R2300)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Rural and Regional Studies Institute, 1972-1983 (Box R2301)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Social Sciences training, 1976-1984 (Box R2302)
      - Gadjah Mada University - SOSPOL - teaching materials, 1978-1984 (Box R2302)
  - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries, 850
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - Philippines, 242
      - Asian Institute of Management - Management research, 1977-1983 (Box R2302)
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 86), 1965-1991; bulk; 1.12; 67.2 Cubic Feet; 56 standard record storage boxes - Box R2305-R2360.
  Files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1986.
  - International, 100
    - Population - Conference (also (A83)), 1975-1977 (Box R2305)
  - Agricultural Institutes, 104
    - Agricultural Institutes - Biotechnology Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2306)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - Academic Profession - Conference, 1981-1985 (Box R2306)
    - American History from Abroad - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2306)
    - Anti-Progestational Activity - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2306)
    - British Capitalism & Caribbean Slavery - Conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2306)
    - Crisis in the Steel Industry - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2306)
    - Crop Production Improvement - Conference, 1980-1985 (Box R2306)
    - Currency Comparison - Conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2307)
    - Cycles in Chinese Economic History - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2307)
    - East German and American Views on the Reformation - Conference (not held), 1984-198[?] (Box R2307)
    - Europe in a Changing World - Conference, 1980-1984 (Box R2307)
    - Experimenting with Scale - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2307)
    - Folklore and the State - Conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2307)
    - Healing Role of the Arts - Conference, 1980-1985 (Box R2307)
    - Income Transfer and the Poor - Conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2308)
    - International Philanthropy and the Humanities - Conference (& supplementary material), 1981-1984 (Box R2308)
    - Lawyers in Society - Conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2308)
    - Medicine and Aging - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2308)
    - Nuclear War: Consequences and Prevention - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2308)
    - Politico-Military Relations - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2308)
    - Population Growth and Labor - Conference, 1982-1984 1991 (Box R2308)
    - Privacy and Data Protection - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2308)
    - Protection of the World's Children - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2308)
    - Red Blood Cell Carriers - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2308)
    - Scholars - Alexander, Alan, 1983-1985 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Anderson, Thomas J., 1982-1984 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Apfel, Roberta J., 1983-1985 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Barr, James, 1983-1985 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Baum, Warren C., 1983-1984 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Beaton, Janet I., 1983-1984 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Behler, Ernst, 1983-1984 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Belitt, Ben, 1983-1985 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Berliner, P.F., 1982-1985 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Boeninger, Edgardo, 1982-1984 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Bok, Derek C., 1983-1984 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Bok, Sissela, 1983-1984 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Brewer, J. (did not go), 1982-1983 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Caltabiano, R., 1982-1985 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Chayes, A.J., 1982-1984 (Box R2309)
    - Scholars - Dugger, R., 1983-1984 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Elliott, W. and D.C., 1982-1984 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Farber, T.D., 1983-1984 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Field, J.O., 1982-1985 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Friedman, H., 1983-1985 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Gardner, C., 1983-1985 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Gomez-Pompa, 1983-1985 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Gordon, L., 1982-1985 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Gurkan, I., 1982-1984 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Hansen, R.G., 1983-1984 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Hardi, P., 1983-1984 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Harnack, C., 1983-1985 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Hoffman, L.W., 1983-1984 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Hollander, P., 1983 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Jacker, Corinne, 1984-1985 (Box R2310)
      did not go
    - Scholars - Janis, Irving L., 1983-1985 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - King, Bruce A., 1982-1985 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Kitzmiller, James B., 1983-1984 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Knecht, Robert W., 1983-1985 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Koss, Joan D., 1982-1985 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Kriegel, Gail, 1983-1985 (Box R2310)
    - Scholars - Lesser, Wendy C., 1983-1985 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - Lipton, Judith E., 1983-1985 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - Lodge, David J., 1982-1984 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - McCormick, John O., 1981-1984 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - McHugh, Heather, 1983-1984 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - Miller, William L., 1982-1984 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - Morley, Hilda, 1983-1984 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - Nash, Roderick, 1982-1984 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - Nicholson, John L., 1981-1985 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - Nyhan, William L., 1982-1984 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - Oakes, J., 1982-1983 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - Odell, Peter R., 1983-1985 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - Pelc, Jerzy, 1981 1983-1984 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - Perusse, Roland I., 1983-1984 (Box R2311)
    - Scholars - Plaskow, M., 1983-1985 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Powell, D.H., 1983-1984 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Rapp, Fred, 1979 1982-1983 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Ray, D.E., 1981-1985 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Razafindralandy, S., 1982-1985 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Rifka, Fuad, 1983-1985 1991 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Rorty, Amelie O., 1983-1984 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Rosen, George, 1983-1985 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Rubin, Alan A., 1982-1985 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Saravanamuttu, J., 1983-1985 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Schneebaum, Tobias, 1982-1985 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Schultz, Stephen W., 1982-1984 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Schwartz, Ruth, 1983-1984 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Shea, Daniel B., 1983-1984 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Shehadi, Fadlou A., 1983-1984 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Simon, Bennett, 1982-1984 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Simpson, Eileen, 1983-1984 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Smith, Wilfred C., 1983-1985 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Spencer, Elizabeth, 1982-1991 (Box R2312)
    - Scholars - Spindel, Cheywa R., 1981 1983-1985 (Box R2313)
    - Scholars - Stevens, Rosemary A, 1983-1985 (Box R2313)
    - Scholars - Tankut, G., 1983-1985 (Box R2313)
    - Scholars - Turnbull, C.H., 1982-1984 (Box R2313)
    - Scholars - Vatuk, S.D., 1983-1984 (Box R2313)
    - Scholars - Verba, S., 1982-1984 (Box R2313)
    - Scholars - Weisblat, A., 1983-1984 (Box R2313)
    - Scholars - Wellington, H.H., 1982-1984 (Box R2313)
    - Scholars - Werfel, G.S., 1983-1985 (Box R2313)
    - Scholars - Wiles, M.F., 1982-1983 (Box R2313)
    - Scholars - Williamson, R.C., 1983-1984 (Box R2313)
    - Scholars - Youngson, A.J., 1983-1985 (Box R2313)
    - Societal Aging - Conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2313)
    - Sub Saharan Africa - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2313)
    - Taxation of Controlled Foreign Corporations - Conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2313)
    - Theater Research - Conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2313)
    - Transformation of European Society - Conference, 1980 1982-1984 (Box R2313)
    - Women & the Industrial Process - Conference, 1979 1981-1985 (Box R2313)
    - Women & Men in Modern Agriculture - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2313)
    - Women & Reproductive Care - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2313)
    - Women's Organizations, 1983-1985 (Box R2313)
    - World Food Council - World Food & Hunger Problems Conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2314)
  - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy, 150
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - California, 205
      - University of Southern California - Linear Models Manual, 1980-1985 (Box R2314)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Maryland, 223
      - Chow, Lien-Ping, 1981-1985 (Box R2314)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Colombia, 311
      - University of the Andes - Conference on Women, 1983-1985 (Box R2314)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Mexico, 323
      - Rabago de Rodriguez, Aurora, 1981-1984 (Box R2314)
  - Demographic Evaluation Projects, 151
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - India, 464
      - Lucknow University - Demographic evaluation, 1978 (Box R2314)
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - Nigeria, 497
      - Nukunya, Godwin K., 1980-1984 (Box R2314)
  - 172
    - Sungshin Women's University - Oocyte maturation, 1981-1985 (Box R2321)
  - 175
    - 175 - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Chatters, Linda M., 1982-1984 (Box R2322)
      - Chavez, Leo R., 1983-1984 (Box R2322)
      - Del Valle, Manuel, 1983-1984 1986 (Box R2322)
      - Dickerson, Dennis, 1983-1985 (Box R2322)
      - Garcia, Homer D.C., 1983-1985 (Box R2322)
      - Hampton, Robert L., 1983-1985 (Box R2322)
      - Harrison, Roderick Joseph, 1983-1985 (Box R2322)
      - Henderson, Lenneal J., Jr., 1981 1983-1985 (Box R2322)
      - Joe, Jennie R., 1983-1985 (Box R2322)
      - Lin, Chien, 1983-1985 (Box R2323)
      - Locay, Luis, 1983-1985 (Box R2323)
      - Pouncy, Hilliard W., 1983-1985 (Box R2323)
      - Scott, Joseph Walter, 1983-1984 (Box R2323)
  - U.S. Immigration and Refugee Project, 181
    - American Council for Nationalities Service - Public opinion toward refugees & immigrants, 1983-1985 (Box R2323)
    - Bartel, Ann P., 1982-1983 1985 (Box R2323)
    - Carnegie Endowment - Immigration panel, 1982-1984 (Box R2323)
  - 199
    - University of Alabama - Gossypol, 1982-1983 (Box R2323)
  - United States, 200
    - Academy of Natural Sciences - River ecosystems, 1976-1984 1991 (Box R2323)
    - African-American Institute, Inc.- Women in Southern Africa Conference, 1982-1984 199[?] (Box R2324)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Science, Technology and Women, 1983-1985 (Box R2324)
    - Association of Women & Development - Conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2324)
    - Bryant Park Restoration Corp., 1980-1985 (Box R2324)
    - Catholic University, Washington - Affirmative action, 1983-1985 1991 (Box R2324)
    - Center for Communication - Global Issues seminar, 1982-1985 (Box R2324)
    - Claremont University Center - Humanities Program, 1986 (Box R2324)
    - Coalition of National Voluntary Organizations, 1979-1983 (Box R2324)
    - Commission on Western Hemisphere Foreign Debt and Public Policy, 1983-1984 (Box R2325)
    - Cornell University - Insect control, 1970-1985 (Box R2325)
    - Cornell University - Video programming, 1983-1984 (Box R2325)
    - Development Group for Alternative Policies, 1983-1984 (Box R2325)
    - Fund for the City of New York, Inc. - Non profit Organizations Conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2325)
    - Georgetown University - Rusk fellowships, 1983-1984 (Box R2325)
    - Interlink Press Service - Third World News Service, 1983-1984 (Box R2325)
    - Joint Center for Political Studies - Civil rights leadership conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2325)
    - Kosciuszko Foundation - Polish dictionary, 1983-1985 (Box R2325)
    - McManus, Michael J., 1984-1985 (Box R2326)
    - Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund - Chicano internship, 1973-1978 1980-198[?] (Box R2326)
    - Naleo Education Fund - Hispanic officials directory, 1983-1985 (Box R2326)
    - National Alliance of Black School Educators - Black academic & cultural excellence report, 1984 (Box R2326)
    - National Commission on Student Financial Assistance - Graduate education report, 1983-1984 (Box R2326)
    - National Committee for Full Employment - Jobs impact bulletin, 1980-1985 (Box R2326)
    - National Urban League - Black political handbook, 1982-1985 (Box R2326)
    - New Mexico State University - Native American educational management, 1977-1985 (Box R2326)
    - Phelps-Stokes Fund - Native American philanthropic news service (also [unreadable]), 1983-1985 (Box R2326)
    - Randolph Educational Fund - Trade union interns, 1978-1985 (Box R2326)